Jérémy Zangla

Graduate Student

: 22 rue Saint-Martial, 63730 Les Martres-de-Veyre, France

☐ : zangla.jeremy@gmail.com

gagoi : 🖸

U: +336 06 49 76 29

Jérémy Zangla : 🛅

Personal Details

Organized and practical student, I am currently learning about software engineering at ISIMA. During my degree. I worked really hard in order to do my best despite the deadlines. I have worked on team projects academically and by myself to improve my abilities and my knowledge. Through my involvement in the student life, I created relationships with students from other disciplines and worked successfully with them in several personal projects. I am searching for a 5 months internship in a good work environment so that i will expand my abilities and learn new working method.

Experiences

2015 - Present Family business (asparagus production), Les Martres-de-Veyre (63), France.

- Organized work with several constraints (weather, staff availability, etc.).
- Analyzed and fixed bottlenecks in the old processing method.
- Researched how to optimize fertilizer's usage and accomplished better yield.
- Sold the production at the market.

2018 - Present

Treasurer, *Isibot* (*ISIMA*'s robotics club).

- Established a quote of our projects and negotiated funding with the student organization.
- Participated in class to help new members with the basics of robotics.

Education and Training

2018 - Present

(2021)

Diplôme d'ingénieur en informatique, ISIMA, Clermont-Ferrand (63), France.

Equivalent to Master's Degree in Engineering. Currently in second year with option F2: Software Engineering & Information Systems

- Built a sumo-bot as an academic project in pairs (2019) :
 - Designed and assembled the robot.
 - Defined a strategy in adequacy with our sensors and motors.
 - Made a report on the project and how to improve it.

2016 - 2018Prep'ISIMA, UCA & ISIMA, Clermont-Ferrand (63), France.

Two-year preparatory course for direct entry into ISIMA carried out in conjunction with year 1 and 2 of the UCA Computer Science degree course.

- Built a line following robot as an academic project in pairs (2018) :
 - Used a purchased base as a starter.
 - Developed and implemented the algorithm.
 - Achieved a functional robot with good performances.

2013 - 2016 Baccalauréat Scientifique, Lycée Lafayette, Clermont-Ferrand (63), France.

Equivalent to British A levels

- Developed a 2D Game library as an academic project in pairs (2016 2015) :
 - Learned how to create library in java.
 - Succeeded implement all the planned features and made a test game.

Jérémy Zangla

Graduate Student

Skills and Qualifications

Languages

French Native

English Moderate

German Basic

Computer Tools

- o Git o Eclipse o Arduino IDE
- Word
 Visual Studio Code
 Mbed platform
- Excel
 Android Studio
 Catch2 framework
- PowerPointSublime TextValgrind

Computer Science

- Java (Expert) O LaTeX (Novice) JavaScript (Novice)
- \circ \bigcirc C++ (Intermediate) \circ \bigcirc Ocaml (Novice) \circ \bigcirc CSS3 (Novice)
- Python (Novice)
 Scheme (Novice)
 SQLite (Intermediate)

Miscellaneous

- Participated in 6 game jams
 - Developed with a lot of technologies (Java, C++, C, JS, JSON).
 - Used a lot of software (Gimp, Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, Git, Sublime Text).
 - Worked as a team of 2, 3 or 5 members.
 - Participated in Global Game Jam in 2019.
- Worked on some personal games
- Jogging (twice a week)
- Hand'Tutorat
 - Academic help to disabled pupils in local secondary schools.
 - Met once a week with the main goal of improving results and making them pass their Baccalauréat.

References

References available upon request.